[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[LAUGHING, SNORTING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are playing
hide-and-seek.
It is George's turn to hide.
He must quickly
find somewhere to hide
before Peppa
finishes counting.
One, two, three...
four, five,
six, seven...
[GIGGLES]
George has found somewhere
to hide just in time.
...10.
[SNORTS]
Ready or not,
here I come.
Peppa has to find
where George is hiding.
[SNORTS]
Found you.
Peppa has found George.
George, I could
see you too easily.
[SNORTS]
Now it is Peppa's turn
to hide.
One...um...three.
I'll help George
to count.
[SNORTS]
One, two, three...
four, five...
six, seven,
eight,
nine, 10.
Okay, George,
open your eyes.
[SNORTS]
George has to find
where Peppa is hiding.
Oh.
Peppa isn't hiding
under the table.
[SNORTS]
DADDY PIG:
George.
Have you thought
of looking upstairs?
[♪♪]
[GIGGLES]
Peppa isn't under the bed.
[SNORTS]
What was that
strange noise?
Peppa isn't behind
the curtain.
[SNORTS]
There is that strange noise
again.
What can it be?
[GIGGLING]
Whee!
[BLOWS RASPBERRY, SNORTS]
George has found
where Peppa was hiding.
George found me.
Now it is Daddy's turn
to hide.
I think George should have
another turn.
[SNORTS]
But George isn't
very good at hiding.
I'm sure he'll be better
this time.
Close your eyes
and start counting.
One, two, three, four...
Oh, dear.
Peppa will easily find George.
...five...
George, come over here.
PEPPA:
...eight...
...nine, 10.
[SNORTS]
Ready or not,
here I come.
[♪♪]
Oh. George isn't hiding
under the table.
[SNORTS]
But George always hides
under the table.
Have you thought
of looking upstairs?
[SNORTS]
I know where he is!
George is in
the toy basket.
[♪♪]
Oh.
George is not
in the toy basket.
Where can he be?
Peppa cannot find George
anywhere.
Daddy, I can't find
George anywhere.
Oh, dear.
I wonder where he can be.
[GEORGE GIGGLING]
[SNORT]
Actually,
I think there's something
about George in this newspaper.
[GEORGE LAUGHING]
[GRUNTS]
Whee!
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
George! Found you!
[LAUGHS, GRUNTS]
Oh, George, that was
a good place to hide.
[ALL LAUGHING]
George was hiding behind Daddy
Pig's newspaper all the time.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY, GIGGLES]
[♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are going
to the playgroup.
It is George's first day.
George, are you looking
forward to the playgroup?
[SNORTS]
Daddy, maybe George is too small
to go to my playgroup.
[SNORTS]
He'll be fine, Peppa.
There'll be you and Mr. Dinosaur
there to keep him company.
Grrr, dinosaur.
[GIGGLES]
But I want to play
with the big children,
not George and his
toy dinosaur.
Oh, dear. Peppa doesn't want
George to go to her playgroup.
[SCHOOL BELL TOLLS]
We're here.
Daddy, are you sure
George is big enough?
He'll be fine.
[SNORTS]
All right.
He can come.
[SNORTING]
[LAUGHS]
Bye-bye.
[SNORTS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Woof, woof!
Madame Gazelle looks after
the children at the playgroup.
PEPPA [SNORTING]:
Hello!
This is my little brother,
George.
[KIDS LAUGH]
Hello, George.
[ALL MAKING ANIMAL NOISES]
[LAUGHS]
[BLEATS]
I wish I had a little brother
like George.
Really?
Hello, I'm Danny Dog.
[BARKS]
Is that a dinosaur?
[SNORTS]
It's just a toy dinosaur.
Grrr, dinosaur.
Brilliant.
[BARKS]
Dinosaur. Grrr.
[ALL SCREAM]
[CHUCKLES]
Dinosaur. Grrr.
Ah, really scary.
[ALL LAUGH]
That's brilliant.
[SNORTS]
George is my brother.
He's brilliant.
[SNORTING]
Peppa is proud of her
little brother George.
[CLAPS]
[KIDS GIGGLING]
Shall we show George
how we paint pictures?
George is not very good
at painting.
Well, maybe you could
help him.
[SNORTS]
Yes. I'm very good.
I will show him
how to paint a flower.
George, today
I'm going to teach you
how to paint a flower.
[SNORTS]
First you paint
a big circle.
No, George,
that's the wrong color.
[SNORTS]
Now you paint
the flower's petals.
George!
[SNORTS]
That's the wrong shape.
Now you paint the stalk
and the leaves.
[SNORTS]
Perfect.
George, you've done it
all wrong.
Now, what do we have here?
[SNORTS]
I've painted a flower.
MADAME GAZELLE:
That's very good, Peppa.
And George has painted
a dinosaur.
Grrr. Dinosaur.
[KIDS LAUGH]
[BARKS]
Brilliant.
I think George and Peppa's
pictures should go on the wall.
ALL: Hooray!
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa, you must be very proud
of your little brother.
[SNORTS]
Yes, I am.
[MAKING ANIMAL NOISES]
It is home time,
and the children's parents
are here to pick them up.
[SNORTS]
Can George come next time?
Yes. And he can paint us
another lovely picture.
And what will you paint
next time, George?
Dinosaur. Grrr.
Oh! Another dinosaur
picture?
Well, maybe you can show us all
how to paint a dinosaur.
[SNORTS]
[BARKS]
Brilliant.
Yes. Brilliant.
[SNORTS]
Brilliant.
[ALL LAUGH]
[BIRDS TWEETING]
[♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
NARRATOR:
Mommy Pig is working
on her computer.
[♪♪]
Daddy Pig is making soup
for lunch.
[SNORTS]
Daddy?
Can we go and watch
Mommy on her computer?
Yes, as long as
you don't disturb her.
She has a lot of important
work to do today.
[SNORTS]
Thank you, Daddy!
[BOTH LAUGH]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Mommy Pig has a lot
of important work to do.
[SNORTS]
Mommy.
Can George and I
sit on your lap
and watch you work?
Yes. If you both
sit quietly.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Peppa and George love to watch
Mommy work on the computer.
Mommy? Can we play
that computer game,
"Happy Mrs. Chicken?"
[SNORTS]
We can play,
"Happy Mrs. Chicken" later.
But now I have to work.
Mommy, can we
help you work?
No, Peppa. You mustn't
touch the computer.
[SNORTS]
And George,
you mustn't touch
the computer either.
Yes, George.
You mustn't do this.
Peppa, stop!
[SNORTS]
Sorry, Mommy.
I was just showing George
what not to do.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Oh, dear. The computer
is not meant to do that.
Daddy Pig!
What is it, Mommy Pig?
[BEEPING]
Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
Can you mend the computer?
Um...
I'll finish the lunch,
while you mend the computer.
Uh...right you are,
Mommy Pig.
But I'm not very good
with these things.
Oh, thank you,
Daddy Pig.
Daddy Pig is going
to mend the computer.
Hmm.
[BEEPING]
Um, maybe if I just
switch it off...
and then switch it on again.
Daddy Pig has mended
the computer.
Hooray, Daddy!
[SNORTS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Yes, I am a bit of an expert
at these things.
[SNORTS]
Daddy?
Can we play that computer game,
"Happy Mrs. Chicken?"
Maybe you should ask
Mommy Pig.
Mommy said that we can
play it later.
Well, that's okay, then.
But I don't know
where the disc is.
[SNORTS]
[SNORTING]
[CHICKEN CLUCKS]
[CLUCKING]
Yippee!
[SNORTS]
[SNORTING]
[CHUCKLES]
[♪♪]
[CLUCKS, PASSES GAS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Now it's my turn.
[♪♪]
[CLUCKS, PASSES GAS]
[ALL GIGGLING]
[LAUGHS]
Now it's my turn.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[♪♪]
[CLUCKING, PASSING GAS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
What on earth is going on?
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
[CLUCKS, PASSES GAS]
Well, I see the computer
is working again.
[CHICKS CLUCKING]
[LAUGHS, SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[ALL CLUCKING]
[ALL PASSING GAS]
[♪♪]
[PEPPA READS ONSCREEN TEXT]
[GIGGLING, GRUNTS]
NARRATOR:
George is playing with his ball
in the garden.
[SNORTS]
Peppa wants to play too.
George, you're doing it
all wrong!
This is how
to catch a ball.
[SNORTS]
Not like this.
[SNORTS LOUDLY]
[GIGGLING]
That's what you do.
What a cheeky little one
Peppa is.
[SNORTS, LAUGHS]
George, come back,
you little piggy.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[LAUGHS]
Maybe Peppa is teasing George
just a bit too much.
Peppa, have you been
teasing George?
Not really, Mommy.
I was teaching him how to catch.
MOMMY PIG:
Really?
Oh, well, I know a game that
will teach George how to catch.
It's called
piggy in the middle.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Peppa, you take the ball
and stand over there.
And, George,
you stand over there.
Good.
You have to throw the ball
to each other,
and I have to try
and catch it.
I'm the piggy
in the middle.
[GIGGLES]
♪ Mommy is the
Piggy in the middle ♪
[PEPPA AND GEORGE LAUGH]
Catch, George.
Oh. Missed it.
[SNORTS]
George has caught the ball.
Hooray!
[BOTH LAUGH]
Well done, George.
Now you throw the ball
to Peppa.
Oop, try again.
Oh, try again.
George cannot throw the ball
past Mommy Pig.
Come on, George,
give the ball to me.
[SNORTS]
Oh!
[ALL LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
Silly George.
[GIGGLES]
I can do that too.
[LAUGHING]
Oh!
[SNORTS]
Peppa wanted
to copy George,
but she's too big
and has got stuck.
[SNORTS AND CHUCKLES]
I've got the ball.
Peppa, now it's your turn
to be piggy.
George, catch.
[SNORTS]
MOMMY PIG & PEPPA: Hooray!
Caught it!
George, you're the piggy.
[GIGGLES]
George, catch!
[ALL LAUGH]
Catch the ball,
George.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
Catch, George!
George, catch.
[GIGGLES AND SNORTS]
Here's the ball,
George.
[GIGGLES AND SNORTS]
Wee!
[CRIES]
MOMMY PIG:
Oh, dear.
Peppa, you shouldn't
tease George like that.
[WHIMPERING]
Sorry, George.
What's all the noise?
Daddy, George is too little
to play piggy in the middle.
Oh, I'm sure
he's big enough.
No, he isn't, Daddy.
Watch.
Catch it, George.
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
That's not fair!
Yes, it is. I just gave George
a helping hand.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Mommy, can I have
a helping hand?
Of course you can, Peppa.
[GIGGLES AND SNORTS]
To me, George!
Catch, George.
[LAUGHS]
Peppa loves
catching the ball.
George loves catching
the ball.
Everyone loves
catching the ball.
[ALL LAUGHING AND SNORTING
[♪♪]
[GIGGLING AND SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING]